Guide to the Freewater Production Films and Records, 1967-2003 and undated UA.09.13.0005
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Freewater Film records1967-2003, 9 boxes
  This series contains the paper records and publicity for Freewater Films spanning most of its history. Includes programming notes, film proposals, publicity, memoranda, and other subject files.
  - Visual Arts Committee: Student Union Fim Series, 1967 (Box 41)
  - Genesis Films, circa 1969 (Box 41)
  - Film Reviews, 1970s (Box 41)
  - Printed Matter, 1972-1979 (Box 41)
  - Board, Administrative papers 1972-1973 (Box 41)
  - [Publicity, Structural Document], circa 1972-1981 (Box 41)
  - [Publicity Flyers], 1973 March-April (Box 41)
  - The Conformist, 1972 (Box 41)
  - Zipporah Films, 1972 (Box 41)
  - Woodstock, 1972 (Box 41)
  - The Paper Chase, 1973 (Box 41)
  - Genesis 5, 1973 (Box 41)
  - Film Showing Reports, 1973 (Box 41)
  - Graphic Arts Committee; Freewater Committee, 1975 (Box 41)
  - Freewater, 1975 (Box 41)
  - On Showing the Devil in Miss Jones, 1975 (Box 41)
  - Frey Proposal, 1975-1976 (Box 41)
  - Summer Programming, 1975-1978 (Box 41)
  - Miscellaneous, 1977-1978 (Box 41)
  - Summer Programming, 1977 (Box 41)
  - Dean Fein's Proposed Policy; Union's Response, 1977 (Box 41)
  - Confirmations, 1977 (Box 41)
  - Children's Film Series, 1977 (Box 41)
  - Budgets, 1978 (Box 41)
  - General, 1979 (Box 42)
  - Freewater Committee [Extensive material on policy re: X-rated films], [1972-1977] (Box 42)
  - Newpaper Clippings, 1976-1977 (Box 42)
  - Confirmations, 1978 (Box 42)
  - General, 1978 (Box 42)
  - Film Showings, 1978-1979 (Box 42)
  - General Info - Summer Programming, 1978 (Box 42)
  - Budget, 1979 (Box 42)
  - Renovations of room 010 Old Chem, 1979 (Box 42)
  - General, 1979 (Box 42)
  - Policy Concerning Films at Duke, Bill Griffith, 1979 May 11 (Box 42)
  - 1978 Children's Film Series, 191978 (Box 42)
  - Spring Films, 1979 (Box 42)
  - Miscellaneous, 1978-1979 (Box 42)
  - Proposal for Showing Andy Warhol's Dracula, circa 1979 (Box 42)
  - Freewater Children's Series, Spring, 1979 (Box 42)
  - Freewater Children's Series, Fall, 1979 (Box 42)
  - Filmmaking Persons, 1979-1980 (Box 42)
  - Freewater Film Society, Fall, 1979 (Box 42)
  - Freewater Film Society, Spring, 1980 (Box 42)
  - Materials for Fall Poster, 1979 (Box 42)
  - General Correspondence, circa 1980 (Box 42)
  - Duke Marine Lab, 1981 (Box 42)
  - Community TV Budgets, 1981-1982 (Box 42)
  - Perkins Library Film Checkout, 1981 (Box 42)
  - Leslie Nydick Grant Proposal, 1981 (Box 42)
  - Ellen Theg's Agreement w/ Union, 1981 (Box 42)
  - Grant Application, 1981 (Box 42)
  - "The World According to Garp", 1982 (Box 42)
  - Freewater, circa 1983 (Box 42)
  - General Records, circa 1983-1985 (Box 42)
  - American Pictures, 1985 March 20 (Box 42)
  - Freewater Grant Procedures Filmmakers - Jose Berger, 1979-1980 (Box 42)
  - Insurance w/ Duke - Equipment, circa 1980 (Box 43)
  - Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 43)
  - Photosynthesis, 1980 October 10 (Box 43)
  - License to Videotape Community TV, 1980-1981 (Box 43)
  - Freewater Films in Bio-Science, 1978-1980 (Box 43)
  - Baldwin Auditorium, 1974-1982 (Box 43)
  - Schedule, 1981-1982 (Box 43)
  - Budget Info + Schedule, 1982-1983 (Box 43)
  - Miscellaneous, Grants, 1982-1984 (Box 43)
  - Dubbing, 1984-1985 (Box 43)
  - X-rated Film, 1982 (Box 43)
  - Schedule, 1983 (Box 43)
  - Script for Student Film "Darkmoor", 1982-1983 (Box 43)
  - General Records, 1983 (Box 43)
  - Minutes + Memos, 1983 (Box 43)
  - Publicity, 1983-1984 (Box 43)
  - Presentations, 1984 (Box 43)
  - Grant Applications, 1984 (Box 43)
  - General Records, 1985-1986 (Box 43)
  - Presentations, 1985-1986 (Box 43)
  - Presentations, 1986-1987 (Box 43)
  - General, 1986-1987 (Box 43)
  - "Out of Bounds", 1986-1987 (Box 44)
  - DUU Commercial, 1986 (Box 44)
  - Grant Applications, 1987-1988 (Box 44)
  - General, 1987-1988 (Box 44)
  - Publicity, 1987-1988 (Box 44)
  - Grant Applications, 1987-1988 (Box 44)
  - General, 1988-1989 (Box 44)
  - General Records, 1990-1991 (Box 44)
  - Grant Applications, 1990-1991 (Box 44)
  - Publicity, 1990-1991 (Box 44)
  - Allie Light, 1992 (Box 44)
  - Grant Applications, Spring, 1992 (Box 44)
  - Presentations, 1987-1988 (Box 44)
  - General, 1988-1993 (Box 44)
  - Grants, Spring, 1989 (Box 44)
  - Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 44)
  - Schedule Books, 1988-1989 (Box 44)
  - Cosponsorships, 1988-1989 (Box 44)
  - Christine Choy,1989 February 13-14 (Box 44)
  - Woods Off the Highway, 1989 February 1 (Box 44)
  - General, 1989-1990 (Box 44)
  - Special Screenings - Premiers and First Runs, 1989-1990 (Box 44)
  - Carolee Schneeman, 1989-1990 (Box 44)
  - Thom Mount, 1989-1990 (Box 44)
  - Production Workshops, 1989-1990 (Box 44)
  - Grant Applications, Spring, 1990 (Box 44)
  - Miscellaneous, 1989-1992 (Box 44)
  - Depreciation, 1997 (Box 44)
  - Budget + Schedule, 1997-1998 (Box 44)
  - Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 45)
  - Programming, 1995-1996 (Box 45)
  - Grant Applications, 1994-1995 (Box 45)
  - General, 1994-1995 (Box 45)
  - Film Schedule, 1993 (Box 45)
  - Programming, 1993 (Box 45)
  - Grant Applications, Fall, 1992 (Box 45)
  - North Davis Proposal, 1992-1993 (Box 45)
  - Permanent File, 1992-1993 (Box 45)
  - Southern Circuit, 1992-1993 (Box 45)
  - Membership, 1991-1992 (Box 45)
  - Press Releases, 1991-1992 (Box 45)
  - General, Fall, 1992 (Box 45)
  - General, Fall, 1990 (Box 45)
  - Proposals, 1998 (Box 45)
  - Publicity Posters, 1999-2004 (Box 46)
  - Publicity, 1999 (Box 46)
  - Publicity, 1998 (Box 46)
  - Publicity, 1997 (Box 46)
  - Publicity, 1996 (Box 46)
  - Publicity, 1995 (Box 46)
  - Publicity, 1994 (Box 46)
  - Publicity, 1993 (Box 46)
  - Publicity, 1992 (Box 46)
  - Publicity, 1990 (Box 46)
  - Publicity, 1989 (Box 46)
  - Publicity, 1988 (Box 46)
  - Publicity, 1987 (Box 46)
  - Publicity, 1986 (Box 46)
  - Publicity, 1985 (Box 46)
  - Publicity, 1984 (Box 46)
  - Publicity, 1980 (Box 46)
  - Film Proposals, 1971-1993 (Box 46)
  - Film Proposals, 1991-1993 (Box 46)
  - Film Proposals, 1988-1992 (Box 47)
  - Film Proposals, 1974-1995 (Box 47)
  - Budget, 1989-1993 (Box 47)
  - Budget, 1993-1996 (Box 47)
  - Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 47)
  - Requisitions, 1997 (Box 47)
  - Requisitions, 1997 (Box 47)
  - Requisitions, 1997-1998 (Box 47)
  - Film Reports, 1997 (Box 47)
  - Film Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 47)
  - Box Office Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 48)
  - Invoices, 1997 (Box 48)
  - Invoices, 1997 (Box 48)
  - Audience Reports, 2005 (Box 48)
  - Administrative Files, 2005 (Box 48)
  - Box Office Reports, Shipping Invoices, 2004-2005 (Box 48)
  - Film Sketches, Undated (Box 48)
  - Film Ballots, Undated (Box 48)
  - Quadfix Ballots, Undated (Box 48)
  - Rudy Proposal, 1993 (Box 48)
  - Major Attractions, 2002-2003 (Box 48)
  - Weekly Stuff, 2002 (Box 48)
  - Contact Info, 2002 (Box 48)
  - Contacts, 2002 (Box 48)
  - K-Ville Kares Concert, 2003 February (Box 48)
  - Publicity + Budget, 2002-2003 (Box 48)
  - Event Advising Center, 2002 (Box 48)
  - Subcommittees, 2002 (Box 48)
  - "Freewater Presentations," 1983 series (oversize poster on foam core) (Box Oversize Folder 1)
- Freewater Films: UA2014-0038
  - Oblivion, April 1986 (Box 48)
  - Muffin Man (film screenplay), 1985 (Box 48)